products I regret buying and the ones I
don't I regret spending over 4000 rupees
on the Lancome genifique serum it's a
really basic hydrating Serum with a
little bit of vitamin C and a lot of
alcohol I'd much rather buy the ordinary
peptide serum and the vitamin C for less
than half the price and minus the
alcohol the anomaly leave-in conditioner
doesn't just have a very inconvenient
packaging but it weighs my hair down I
prefer the L'Oreal no haircut cream it
has a convenient packaging tames frizz
and offers heat protection I spent a
bomb on fenty's icon liquid lipstick in
the shade MVP it does have a really
comfortable formulation but it literally
transfers everywhere however the K
Beauty liquid lipstick in the shade
treasure does not transfer at all and
feels really comfortable on the lips as
well I don't see the point of buying
this m caffeine powder sunscreen as per
the Brand's own website this doesn't
have any actual UV filters there's no
data to prove that these ingredients
give any UV protection I'd rather buy
the dermaker powder sunscreen that comes
with recognized mineral filters let me
know if you've got any of these and do
subscribe for more Buy